We all have a side of ourselves
that we don't show anyone.
Whether it's with friends, lovers,
or even family,
we hide our true feelings and true nature
with fake smiles and deception.
And that's how the world maintains
its temporary peace.
Countries worldwide are battling
a discrete yet fierce information war.
Two countries,
East and West, are in a standoff.
Ostania in the east is plotting war.
Westalis in the west is trying to stop it.
Westalis launched
Operation Strix to find out
the movements of
key figures in the Ostania government.
B-1 Agent Twilight,
is in charge of the operation.
This man of a hundred different faces,
has a mission to fulfill.
To create a family.
ORIGINAL WORK BY TATSUYA ENDO
SERIALIZED ON SHUEISHA'S SHONEN JUMP PLUS
OSTANIA CAPITAL BERLINT
WEST WART, PARK STREET
Is this all your stuff?
Yes.
It's not much at all.
Um… Loid, what about the bedroom?
Of course, we'll be in separate rooms.
We'll adjust accordingly
when we have guests.
S… Sure!
Welcome to Anya's home!
I'm excited to live with you, Anya!
This was an unusual family.
The father, Loid Forger,
is a psychiatrist.
He true identity is a spy.
His codename is Twilight.
The mother, Yor Forger,
is a city hall employee.
She is actually an assassin.
Codename is Thorn Princess.
The daughter is Anya Forger.
She is a telepath.
Anya is happy that she has a mother now!
I'll help.
Oh, by the way, I have a connection
with a judge, and he made it so
it looks like we got married a year ago.
The truth is, it was forged.
We'll think of reasons why
we were living apart until now later,
and what to tell your brother.
Okay.
If we got married
right before the interview,
the school would be suspicious.
The shopkeeper gave me his approval,
so I'm relieved.
How exciting!
Father. Mother. Daughter.
For their own personal reasons,
the three of them created
a fake family and live under one roof,
hiding their true identities
from one another.
MISSION:3 PREPARE FOR THE ENTRANCE EXAM
Anya will show Mother around!
Once that's settled,
we're going to practice for the interview.
This is the kitchen!
Father is good at cooking!
I see!
This is the toilet and bath.
It's so clean!
Anya can wash her face by herself.
What a good girl!
This is Anya's room.
Welcome!
May I come in?
What a cute room!
I'll introduce you to Kimera.
I'm Kimera. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you Kimera.
I'm Anya's mother.
This is Father's room!
So this is Loid's room.
Mother's room is over here.
Come in, Mother.
Okay, thank you.
This is my room…
It's such a beautiful room!
I'm glad.
This is all of it.
How is the furniture arrangement?
I also cleaned a bit.
This is perfect.
Anya helped clean too!
Really? Thank you!
Aren't I good? Aren't I a good girl?
All you did was tip over the bucket.
Sorry!
I don't know what to do!
You let me borrow such a beautiful room!
What are you saying?
Think of it as your own home.
In fact, it is your home,
so do as you please.
Thank you!
I'll come get the boxes
once you empty them.
Loid, I'm done putting everything away!
You're so efficient!
Oh, is this your little brother?
Yes.
He's a civil servant like you, correct?
That's right.
He seems quite busy these days,
so I've only spoken to him on the phone.
You two look alike.
Once Anya's exams are over,
I should go introduce myself.
About that, Loid…
I don't have a proper outfit
for the interview…
Then let's go to the dressmaker today.
Thank you!
I'll help.
Anya! I'll do that one!
There's a highly poisonous weapon
in there for work…
KNICK-KNACKS - BEDROOM
-What would you like, Loid?
-Black coffee, please.
Anya wants hot cocoa!
With milk and sugar, right?
Exactly.
Wow, homemade cookies?
It was actually my first time
baking cookies.
I followed the recipe,
so they should be pretty good.
I hope you like them.
Thank you. I'll take one.
They're delicious!
You're really good at cooking!
Not really.
Anya helped with the cookies too!
I see!
All you did was eat peanuts
after you covered yourself in flour.
Why don't we start after our break?
Eden Academy is one of the
top elite schools in the country.
Children and their parents are
screened during the interview process.
Good family character and level of
education are also tested.
Understood? Now, onto the first question.
Please tell me your name and address.
A… Anya F… F… Forger. Address?
For this home.
Anya's home!
That's not what I'm asking.
Anya, what do you do on your days off?
My father orders me to stay home,
so I watch TV all alone.
Wait.
That gives off a bad impression. Mother.
Yes!
Please tell us the reason why you're
dying to enter Eden Academy.
Reason for dying? Um, dying…
Cardiopulmonary arrest
or excessive bleeding or…
complex fractures throughout the body
or skull fractures…
Let me ask another question.
What is your educational policy?
Um, victory goes to the one
who makes the first move?
How did her brother grow up okay?
I've worked for over ten years as a spy.
I've been on numerous missions
and I'm on the verge of breaking down.
There's no way
we'll pass the interview like this.
Let's give up on the school.
Loid! Please remember
your late wife's wish!
Maybe it was too early
for a mock interview.
Okay, let's go out.
First let's broaden our horizons, acquire
general knowledge on upper-class families,
and create a common understanding
among the three of us.
Excur-gen, excur-gen, la la la la!
You mean "excursion."
Mother, want to hold hands?
It's a pleasure!
I'm glad they seem to like each other.
I already have a plan in mind.
By the end of the day, we'll look like a
normal… No, we'll look like a real family.
She reminds me of my brother
when he was small and cute.
I once gave him a big hug
and broke two of his ribs.
I have to be careful.
Huh? What?
Maybe I was wrong.
By the way, where are we headed?
I got a bunch of tickets
through my connections at work.
Eden Academy values
tradition and prestige.
I'll deepen our education
by exposing them to first class things.
We need to make sure
we don't slip up and get caught.
Great. Let's go to the next one.
Anya, you have to be quiet here.
Okay.
After first-class music, the next step is
to be exposed to first-class art and more.
Father! She's completely naked!
Headless, body-less!
I told you to keep it down.
Yor?
Yo--
Anya wants to do that!
Drawing? Okay.
-Yor, shall we take a break?
-Sure.
Anya's home is a huge castle.
The head of the secret organization
is Director Kimera.
Father is a spy.
Mother is an assassin.
Shall we go soon?
Sure.
Finished!
Anya, let's go to the next place.
If they see this, Father and Mother
will find out about my abilities!
Wow, that's a big piece of work.
There's a pig in the forest.
It's Mr. Kimera, who lives in the castle!
I see. But I know that's Bondman.
I'm right, aren't I?
From last week's spy cartoon, right?
Which makes this witch thing a princess?
It's a bit gory. Although the cat is cute.
-It's a dog!
-Oh, sorry.
We'll go to the dressmaker next.
I'm sorry to make you come here
on your day off.
No problem, it's necessary anyway.
Anya's outdoor outfit is so cute!
It's perfect for Anya!
This shop is amazing! I love it!
Thank you.
My first excur-gen wearing this outfit.
Then today is an anniversary!
An excur-gen anniversary!
Then we should stop by
a photo studio after this.
Yor, come this way.
Okay.
If it's semi-formal,
I think this color tone is nice.
What do you think?
I prefer black or red for dresses.
Really? I think
you'll look great in this though.
Then how about this one?
Looking at the amount of stuff
she had for her move,
I thought she didn't
care much about clothes, but…
I see you have a preference for
color coordination.
Oh, no, that's not really the case…
It's beautiful but in case I have to work,
I don't want bloodstains on it…
It looks like Yor finally found
someone nice.
I hope it lasts. I wouldn't want to date
someone with a child.
Looks like you'll have your spare clothes
tailored in time for the interview.
I'm sorry you had to buy so many.
Well, you look nice in colors
other than black and red,
and we'll have more outings in the future.
Excur-gen!
You're a regular at that shop, aren't you?
I'm sure you'll be using
their services again in the future,
so we should tell the storekeeper
about our marriage.
That's right!
Our Nationalist Party takes
a line of appeasement
in its policy toward the West!
Eden Academy also offers
a strong patriotic education.
I need to familiarize her with
politics and history.
Get out of here, you traitor!
My family was killed by them!
-Such lies!
-Give me money!
-What's wrong?
-Anya doesn't like places like this…
I'm sorry, is it a bit scary?
Let's take a break somewhere.
It's all in the East!
That pig!
Father, I'm hungry.
Huh? So, you're well? Which is it?
Hey, Anya. Don't just eat the nuts.
Also, don't eat with your hands.
And you, Yor…
I've worked for over ten years as a spy.
I've been on numerous missions but I'm
on the verge of breaking down again.
Don't worry about it, Father.
Don't worry about what?
I knew I made a mistake
in selecting the right people.
No. It was impossible to
rely on others in the first place.
I shouldn't have entrusted
our success or failure
on others' sense of judgment,
especially amateurs.
The ironclad rule of a spy is to
anticipate every possibility, be prepared,
and act based on careful planning!
So, I need to list every single
possible interview question
and have them both memorize
the perfect answers to them.
-Or, I could try to follow…
-Um…
Loid. How about we relax a little?
The people look like trash.
Where did you learn that?
-Cartoons.
-Hm.
I didn't know there was a park like this
on the outskirts of town.
I only come here sometimes,
like when I'm tired from work…
I feel encouraged when I think that
the work I do
helps these people out there.
This kind of place must be
boring for you! I'm sorry.
Anya likes this better than
a crowded place.
I'm glad!
A robber! Someone help!
What a careless, old woman.
Unforgivable!
Wait up!
We have no other choice.
I've lost him!
Are you okay? Are you injured?
I'm okay. Just a scratch.
I'm going to make sure to catch him,
so I'll take you to the hospital later.
Oh, wow. Thank you.
Oh, I left Loid and Anya…
He's blended in with the crowd.
It's unfortunate for Yor,
but she won't be able to find him now.
-I'm starving!
-That's so expensive.
-How cute!
-How handsome!
Where can I find one million dalcs?
I forgot to pay my rent!
Oh, you're sick again…
That old hag was loaded!
-Father!
-What's wrong?
I want to eat cake!
Huh?
We just left the restaurant! Hm?
That guy…
He's dressed differently,
but he can't change the way he walks.
-Don't think you can fool me.
-Loid!
Mother's here!
Yor! Look after Anya!
With all of this,
I can mess around for a while.
I'll start with a nice meal…
You bastard. Rotten food suits you best.
-What?
-A person just flew down.
A spy must not make a scene.
-I wonder what happened?
-Was anyone watching?
Um, he's a robber, so please
call the police and turn him in.
Thank you for bringing me here.
I had money in there
for a gift for my grandchild.
Thank you so much.
No problem.
The person who got your wallet back
was my husband.
No, if it weren't for Yor,
I wouldn't have even gone after him.
Thank you. What a great man you are.
No, so…
Heroes in the shadows.
Your exploits as agents
will never see the light of day.
Thank you.
I guess it's nice to be
appreciated once in a while.
Father should be more honest.
Thank you, Yor.
Today was a nice change of pace.
I, too, will work hard once again.
Father and Mother are being lovey-dovey.
-No!
Do you have anything to thank Anya for?
Right. We were able to locate the culprit
thanks to your appetite. Good girl.
You're a beautiful family.
Here's a candy for you.
Candy.
Make sure to thank her.
Excur-gen finished!
It was a long day.
Mother!
Anya wants to drink hot cocoa!
Of course!
Hey, we need to try
the mock interview again.
Okay, Anya.
What do you do on your days off?
I go to the opera and the museum,
and I eat at restaurants!
Exactly! That!
If they ask you something,
tell them about today. Next question.
Let's say you saw a friend doing
something bad. What would you do?
I'd fly from above and beat them up
and make them eat rotten food.
Let's pretend you didn't see that part.
This isn't working.
Maybe we should give up.
Father, you were so cool!
Yes, you were!
Pow!
Rotten food!
Cocoa is the best!
You're…
a beautiful family.
If that's what we look like,
I guess I can say that
we finished 1% of our prep work.
MISSION:4
AN INTERVIEW AT A PRESTIGIOUS SCHOOL
Subtitle translation by: Nana Onishi